[Music]
it's
a beautiful day the loop ends are
thriving
casting a delicate shade over the hills
that meld with the soft green of the
sagebrush
here it smells like fresh mint and sweet
florals
it's distinct a scent that always brings
me home to myself
reminding me of who i am
i haven't always considered myself a
happy person
in fact i'd say since my teens i
struggled with constant
ups and downs i didn't realize that as i
grew and matured things would get better
i thought i wasn't capable of finding
balance and peace
there was a reason for feeling this way
and as an adult i saw a doctor and got
help from my body and mind
but i realize that once you finally heal
the wounds of your foundation
you need to rebuild that was the hard
part
i know i've said this before that i
never found a magic solution to feeling
unhappy
at times no matter where you go it
follows you
it followed me here
[Music]
this made me consider that maybe
occasional melancholy is nothing to fear
in fact it has a way of opening your
soul
around us that can remind you of your
beautiful ability to feel
and how alive you truly are
the first thing i had to accept about my
life is that it will never be a
consistent string of joyous blissful
days
there will always be difficult times
though there are ways to get support if
we can seek the help we need
a friend once told me that we are living
memorials to what we have lost
loved ones pets our past selves
for a long time i mourned the loss of a
little girl that was happy
and believed in a bright future i
thought she had been forgotten
in the process of growing up
but i suppose it is our choice to let
the past strengthen or
oppress us and there came a day when i
decided to reclaim the story of that
little girl
and not let her stay in the past she was
still there in my heart
and i could let her guide me to a place
of quiet contentment
now despite the bad days that little
girl comforts me
and tells me everything will be okay and
with that
a seed of happiness continues to grow
taking root
and spreading throughout my world
wishing you a day full of beauty peace
and love
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
so
hi everyone i hope you liked today's
video
i just wanted to give a couple of
announcements
first i'm a little bit behind on
postcards so if you're expecting a
postcard from me
it should be coming your way very soon
but with this week of
kind of setting up my workspace and my
father visiting i got a little bit
behind
um so i just want to let you know and if
for any reason you have
not received a postcard from me and
you've been expecting one please email
me
um now and then i get a postcard sent
back to me in the mail
and it breaks my heart because i email
the person but usually the email i have
is outdated and i just never am able to
get in contact with them
so so please let me know i love to send
out postcards and i really want to
it's it's such a meaningful way for me
to reciprocate
and say thank you to all of you um
last but not least also i wanted to
reiterate that i only have
this one youtube channel and a instagram
account i do not have any other accounts
i noticed recently that a facebook
account popped up
that has been reposting my photos and
using the same name as me and it is
not me so if you're following me on
facebook um
it is not me please don't message that
uh page thinking that i'm gonna reply
because
um i've been trying to get the page
taken down but um i'm just having a
really hard time doing it so
yeah i just i just wanted to give an
announcement that i um i am only
on youtube and instagram and that is it
so anyway um i hope you all have a
wonderful
day or night and that you're all taking
care
and i'm staying safe and healthy sending
my love
goodbye
are you happy see yes
it smells so good
you